>> Kyle Simpson: 正在包装该课程的内容。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Wrapping things up for
this course.
总之，我只能说，不管你决定什么疯狂的理由
In summary, I can simply say, if for
whatever crazy reason you've decided to
你的事业以目前的 JavaScript 为中心
make [LAUGH] your career centered
around JavaScript at this moment,
知道你的 JavaScript是什么意思吗
doesn't it make sense to
know your JavaScript?
更让人好奇的是
Doesn't it make sense to be more curious,
问更多问题想知道密码是怎么工作的
to ask more questions about it,
to want to know why the code works,
这样你就有机会在休息时把它修好吗
so that you have any chance of
trying to fix it when it breaks?
如果认真对待这一点就更有意义了
Doesn't it make more sense
to take it seriously, and
在一段时间里每过一次阅读这个规格，了解，并且有一个心理模型，
read the spec every once in a while and
understand, and have a mental model, and
最重要的是通过对该工具的理解来传达您的想法和
most importantly through the understanding
of that tool communicate your ideas and
你的意图更有效
your intent more effectively.
非常感谢你听我的关于 JavaScript的想法。
Thanks very much for
listening to my thoughts on JavaScript.
我希望当你向前看时你会继续好奇心和
I hope that as you go forward,
you will continue that curiosity and
这种不精确的问题那些问问题的人
that inquisitiveness,
those asking questions.
记住我有很多材料要补充
Remember that I have lots of
materials out there to add to and
支持这项研究
support this particular study.
系列其实是一个很大的资源。
The You Don't Know JS book series
is really a great resource.
所有六本书都可以在 GitHub上阅读。
All six books can be read up on GitHub.
具体来说，本课程的三本书籍将为 " 范围 " 和 " 关闭 "
Specifically, the three books from this
course would be the Scope and Closures
书籍， " 此 " 和 " 对象原型 " 一书，以及 " 类型 " 和 " 语法 " 一书。
book, the This and Object Prototypes book,
and the Types and Grammar book.
所以把这些课题深入到这些课题研究指南中
So use those as your dig deeper
into these topics study guides
从课程之外
from beyond the course.
非常感谢。
Thanks very much.
谢谢你听这些想法
I appreciate you listening
to these thoughts.
>> 受众: [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; Audience: [APPLAUSE]